[{"answer": "Bongiorno.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "Come stai?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "It looks like stuff that were pile on the punt.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "It look like the worst food you can eat right?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Let's see if the audience can guess how many calories in all of this food, six meals.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "What was the total calorie?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "500.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Tangerine (ph) how many?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "2,500.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Andre (ph) how many?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "Well normally the pasta is made with flour which is almost 300 calories in and of itself.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 84, "question": "That's my favorite Italian dish and normally you consume a lot of calories, right?", "qSentId": 83}, {"answer": "OK, so that would be about 710, it's now 190 calories carb-free.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "How many calories?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "It's an unbelievably difficult question to answer, but I think what we're doing right now is part of it.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "How do you culturally change that kind of thinking and the fast food epidemic and so on to get them to start to cook at home in a way that can produce this kind of result?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "I'll tell you one of the reasons I got healthy is because my sex wasn't as good as it should be.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Do you have better sex on your food Rocco?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "I'm 46 years old.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Let me get to this, one question so how old are you?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "6'1\"", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "Two years difference, you're 6'1\" right?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "Almost 230.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "You were at your heaviest how much?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Forty pounds and so, if a chubby chef with a crooked spine and flat feet who could totally get away with it by the way, it's not like girls weren't attracted to me or anything if there was any downside other than the health.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 147, "question": "And you lost how much?", "qSentId": 146}, {"answer": "So you're this unknown guy who just announced he'd been eating a lot of subways and lost a lot of weight and before we know it subway business was completely transformed.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "I'm doing great, Piers how are you?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I do, you know, I don't eat it every single day anymore but I've learned, you know, exactly in moderation.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "Do you still eat subway sandwiches?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Piers, my heaviest I was 320, right now today I got on a scale this morning in the hotel in L.A. I'm 240.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "What were you at your heaviest, what are you now?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "So, what -- I was like a business guy running around the world, doing deals, focused on, you know, building companies.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "And how do you this?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "Sure, well the first thing I'd say Piers is I didn't look at what I did as I diet.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "How have you managed to stay so disciplined?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "I don't know about so much you, but I thought like I need a different perspective.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What you want to become me?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Yes six months.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "So that's you on the left before, that's what you became in the middle?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Six months, yeah, so a year long.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "So, I mean quite extraordinary, that's a six month period?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Never been overweight, never struggled.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 298, "question": "Because you'd never been fat right?", "qSentId": 297}, {"answer": "The biggest things I learned was more so on the mental and emotional side.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "So what were the key takeaways for you?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I think some people looked at me differently, I could see the stares at the grocery store loading up my cart with soda and cereal but no one ...", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Did you suddenly find that, that wasn't happening if you lost it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "No, no one was really mean, but I felt like for my perspective people were staring at me more, so my self esteem, my confidence levels took a hit the bigger I got and so that's the hard part to deal with, lose my self esteem being out in public or getting out of the shower covering up in front of my wife, that's how it affected me.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Oh, Drew loved it, right?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "14 stone, 14 stone.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "What was the point when you went -- how heavy were you when you had enough?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I just felt like where was it going to end.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Was there a moment or kind of self awareness where you went OK that's enough?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I have heard so often people trying to blame people for this problem and I will grant you one moment.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "How do we change the thinking?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "Well our whole country is desperate, so they're desperate but for sure I think it's important to understand this.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "You have seen those and have treated people with those, when it gets to that stage people are pretty desperate aren't they to do something?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Let's do something about it, and he lost, let me ask the audiences, we got to answer this, I want to ask you two questions, the first one is, do you think super sized sodas are good for you?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "But the reality of it is, it's making you sick, whether you have weight problem or not, so stop to think about that for a minute.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "But you don't want to be told you can't have it, how do we get through this?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "It can't hurt but look, you're going to have to be on Tour de France in order, you know, amass the kind of calorie burning that you're going to need to compensate for the kind of over consumption that you can be led.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "A big issue in the sense if you just did half an hour of brisk walking a day, a lot of doctors tell me that that coupled with a reasonable diet is more than enough to exercise?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "Yeah, controlling the intake especially with ...", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 397, "question": "So diet is the key?", "qSentId": 396}, {"answer": "I'm great.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "Tracy, how are you?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "So every time I see one of these celebrities having a baby within about three months they look like a stick ends yet again.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "You know what I support them.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "What you do to these poor women?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Well, that's a little surprise there.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 434, "question": "I think we gave them -- didn't we give them DVD?", "qSentId": 433}, {"answer": "Well, right now Kim is doing what she should be doing which is bonding with her baby.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "What are the key things that women who've had a baby need to do quite quickly to get rid of the baby fat and so on?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Good question.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 514, "question": "What is it about your Barry's Bootcamp is different to others?", "qSentId": 513}, {"answer": "Both.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Can you get properly fit by -- or just doing weights or just doing running is the best combination, both?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "It's indoor cycling.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "What is it and how does it work?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "Yes, it did.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Josh, you actually did the Shaun T Insanity thing and it worked, right?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "I started at 293 and was down to 203.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "What did you end up, the weight?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "What's unique about it is that, you know, well first of all I'd like to say that people are afraid to workout with me because they think it's so hard.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "And what is unique about this?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "A modifier is so and so.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "What is a modifier?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "Yes, kind of.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "So it's a less of Shaun T basically?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "That's a good question because I'm believer in the hour workout.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Barry, do you think as a workout, how many times a week to get reasonably fit?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "Oh, five days a week.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "And how many days a week would you recommend?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "You know, if I can also say.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Barry, you want to go free flagging while you're at it?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "It's a bike.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "So this is like a bike, right?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "I want you to look at that little screen and I want you to take your torque to 25.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 617, "question": "Then what happens?", "qSentId": 616}, {"answer": "Until it gets to 25.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "This one?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "ORGAN: OK.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "That's our word for resistance torque, OK?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "So you're at 25, right?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "Easy.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "You're good?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "This is, you know, getting a little testing.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 649, "question": "How's that going?", "qSentId": 648}, {"answer": "Why not.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Should we try 30?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "That's very good.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "So is that a good balance?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "About 30.", "docId": "131203pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "And how many seconds do I have to keep doing this for?", "qSentId": 658}]